<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
    Artem Tsurkan, n01414146
    Wenyuan Yu, n01403697
    Kyrylo Lvov, n01414058
    Software Project - CENG-322-0NA
-->
<resources>
    <string name="notification_channel">Notification Channel</string>
    <string name="description_of_the_notification_channel">Description of the notification channel</string>
    <string name="housefy_notification_channel">housefy_notification_channel</string>
    <string name="exit_app">Exit App</string>
    <string name="do_you_want_to_exit_the_app">Do you want to exit the app?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="air_conditioner">Air Conditioner</string>
    <string name="air_quality">Air Quality</string>
    <string name="smart_light">Smart Light</string>
    <string name="energy_consumption">Energy Consumption</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="guide">Guide</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="app_name">Housefy</string>
    <string name="app_description">Smart Home Environment and Energy Monitoring System</string>
    <string name="feels_like">Feels like</string>
    <string name="grant_access_to_location_in_order_to_see_weather">Grant access to location in order to see weather</string>
    <string name="one_device">1 device</string>
    <string name="energy_usage">Energy Usage</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="this_month">This month</string>
    <string name="toggle_on_off">Toggle on/off</string>
    <string name="low_speed">Low speed</string>
    <string name="medium_speed">Medium speed</string>
    <string name="high_speed">High speed</string>
    <string name="excellent">Excellent</string>
    <string name="excellent_description">Air quality is satisfactory with minimal or no risk of air pollution.</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="good_description">Air quality is acceptable. Some pollutants may have a moderate impact on a small number of sensitive individuals.</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate</string>
    <string name="moderate_description">Some sensitive individuals may experience health effects. The general public is unlikely to be affected.</string>
    <string name="poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="poor_description">Health effects may occur in the general public, and sensitive groups may experience more severe health issues.</string>
    <string name="air_quality_index">Air Quality Index</string>
    <string name="set_threshold">Set Threshold</string>
    <string name="lock_portrait">Lock Portrait</string>
    <string name="portrait_mode_unlocked">Portrait mode unlocked</string>
    <string name="portrait_mode_locked">Portrait mode locked</string>
    <string name="enable_notifications">Enable Notifications</string>
    <string name="notifications_enabled">Notifications Enabled</string>
    <string name="about_housefy">About Housefy</string>
    <string name="about_line_one">Housefy is an innovative smart home Internet of Things (IoT) application that seamlessly integrates technology into every corner of your home, elevating your everyday living experience.</string>
    <string name="about_line_two">We are dedicated to providing an unparalleled smart home experience that places simplicity, control, and convenience right at your fingertips. With the use of cutting-edge technology, Housefy effortlessly interconnects all your home devices, giving you the power to control and monitor your home, no matter where you are.</string>
    <string name="about_line_three">Our app is designed with a user-friendly interface that makes it easy to manage a variety of home devices. From security systems and lighting controls to thermostats and home appliances, Housefy enables you to run your home in a smarter, more energy-efficient way. Whether you are at home or on the go, Housefy keeps you connected to what`s important the most.</string>
    <string name="about_line_four">Housefy is more than just an app - it`s a lifestyle. It offers the convenience of smart automation, the comfort of energy efficiency and the peace of mind of remote control. It`s your home, but smarter. Welcome to Housefy – embrace the future of home automation.</string>
    <string name="understanding_the_air_quality_index_aqi">Understanding the Air Quality Index (AQI)</string>
    <string name="air_quality_guide">The Air Quality Index, commonly referred to as AQI, is a standard system designed to help you understand the quality of air you breathe. It works by taking real-time data on several key pollutants, such as particulate matter (PM2.5, PM10), nitrogen dioxide, sulfur dioxide, carbon monoxide, and ozone, then converting this data into a simplified score and color code.</string>
    <string name="understanding_energy_consumption">Understanding Energy Consumption</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_one">When we speak of energy consumption, it`s typically measured in kilowatt-hours (kWh). To put it in perspective, a 1,000-watt appliance uses 1 kWh of electricity for one hour of operation. The average energy consumption varies significantly based on location, season, and lifestyle, but we can share some broad estimates based on U.S. and Canadian statistics.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_two">Daily: On average, a U.S. residential utility customer consumes about 30 kWh per day. In Canada, the average daily consumption is about 27 kWh.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_three">Weekly: This scales up to an average of 210 kWh per week in the U.S. and 189 kWh per week in Canada.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_four">Monthly: On a monthly basis, U.S. homes consume around 900 kWh, while in Canada, the average is slightly lower at around 810 kWh.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_five">Yearly: Over a year, the average U.S. home consumes about 10,800 kWh. Canadian homes, on the other hand, consume around 9,720 kWh on average.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_six">Please note that these figures can vary widely based on factors such as the size of the home, the number of occupants, the efficiency of appliances, and more.</string>
    <string name="energy_guide_line_seven">The information and figures provided in this guide are given with the only purpose of helping you understand and interpret the information presented in our app, and can vary significantly depending on a number of factors.</string>
    <string name="feedback_response">Feedback</string>
    <string name="submit_feedback">Submit</string>
    <string name="comment">Comment</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="air_quality_threshold">Air Quality Threshold</string>
    <string name="temperature_threshold">Temperature Threshold</string>
    <string name="dismiss_label">dismiss</string>
    <string name="fullname_error">full name should not beyound 50 characters</string>
    <string name="fullname_error1">full name section should not contain digital numbers</string>
    <string name="email_error">email is beyond 100 characters</string>
    <string name="email_error1">email format is invalid</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_error">phone number is too long</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber_error1">phone number should not contains letters other than digital numbers</string>
    <string name="comment_error">Comment is too long. Must be less than or equal to 200 characters</string>
    <string name="feedback_url">https://housefybackend.azurewebsites.net/api/feedback</string>
</resources>